Anil ji, today I was wasting my time a lot
Anil ji, IEE Loba on which
Anil ji's pick is up, ICICI Loba on which
Ashish had also covered it just now and Anil ji
here also, I mean Morgan Stanley came to know
that I am going to give this pick, then a
stop loss of 1625 has to be placed, a stop loss of 1625 has to be placed
and the target is
17350 and these Anil ji, the decimal targets of D figure have been
taken out so that it appears that
I have done a lot of work on the extended weekend,
okay and all these levels are cash,
which are the April futures, Bansal
ji, Anil ji, all cash's pick of the day, pick of
the week, pick of the series, there are only all cash
levels, ah
ji, okay, so this is for you,
IC Lo is trading around 84,
stop loss of 1625, target of 1, full April,
for the entire month of April, good morning Kunal ji,
welcome